*******Call Spoofing*******
Hello guys, let's get to know something different :)
Earlier there was a call spoofing method but its not working now, But I have come across a new method fully working. Use it to call anyone using anybode else's number. You can also change your voice pitch so that the other person can't recognize you.

Warning-Only for educational purposes.

• 1. Open http://www.crazycall.net/
• 2. Select your country and wait for the page to load.
• 3. Enter the number you want to display in the first big box (Dont change the contents of small box if the fake number is of same country).
• 4. Enter the number you wish to call in
second big box.
• 5. Choose voice pitch as normal (for same
voice) or high or low pitch to change your
voice.
• 6. Click Get me a code.
• 7. Dial the number shown on right and
enter the shown code when asked.