What is cracking software?

Software cracking is the modification of software to remove or disable features which are considered undesirable by the person cracking the software, usually related to protection method: copy protection, trial/demo version, serial number, hardware key, date checks, CD check or software annoyances like nag screens and adware. The distribution and use of cracked copies is illegal in almost every developed country. There have been lawsuits over cracking software.

Who is cracker?

A person who  uses to search for crack files or  tips or tricks over  internet besides cracking software is called cracker.If you do so, then you are a cracker too.

Form where  you can download / upload  crack files?

There are a lot of websites from there you can download any kind of crack files even you can upload there your own crack files for others.

Here are some websites name:

1.www.mediafire.com

2.www. hotfile.com

3.www.thepiratebay.org

4.www. h33t.com

5.www.rapidshare.com

If you want to search crack files in any of these websites or google you can use  the dork below:

    For search in google use this dork : crack:file name   

    For search in various websites use this dork : inurl:forum software name:website name

    For search in torrent use this dork : inurl:torrent intext

Here are some websites addresses where you can find your desire crack files.

Search Engine  Addresses:

1.For rapidshare search :

www.rapidsharesearchengine.com

www.filez.com

2.For media fire search :

www.mediafiresearch.org

www.uvrx.com

3.For hot file search :

www.hotfilesearchengine.com

www.hotfilesearch.com

www.sharedir.com

www.megbase.com

4.For  torrent search :

www.torrentz.com

www.torrentreactor.com

www.torrents.to